peggsandson.com 2018-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE KEEP ON OUR CUSTOMERS AND WHAT WE USE THIS INFORMATION FOR**

We keep information on our customers and newsletter subscribers. We do this to fulfil requests by our customers for goods and services, improve our services, contact our customers, carry out research on our customer’s preferences and to create reports. The information that we collect and store is as follows:

  * We keep the email addresses and names of our newsletter subscribers.
  * We keep the addresses, names, email addresses and phone numbers of people who have purchased an item online with us.
  * We also keep the names and telephone numbers of people who request alterations or personal orders in store.

We never keep any payment data such as credit/debit card numbers. This is held off site by our payment providers, Sagepay and PayPal.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

We never share or sell any information on our customers or subscribers. We use an email marketing provider, MailChimp, to send emails to our newsletter subscribers.

If requested, we will share information with the police in cases of illegal activities such as, but not limited to, suspected fraud and physical violence or threats of physical violence against any of our customers or staff.

**DELETION OF INFORMATION**

If you want any personal information we have on file deleted then please email [infodelete@peggsandson.com](mailto:infodelete@peggsandson.com). This email will be monitored frequently.

You can subscribe from our newsletter at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button in any of our emails. Alternatively you can request that we unsubscribe you by emailing [infodelete@peggsandson.com](mailto:infodelete@peggsandson.com).

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

We limit access to the personal information of our customers to only the employees who we think reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products and services to our customers and to do their jobs effectively.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect personal information about all of our customers and subscribers.

**COOKIES AND ANALYTICS**

This website needs cookies in order to work properly and by using the site you consent to have cookies placed on your computer. As you browse the Peggs & son website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.

This information is then used by our display and retargeting marketing partners to target you with specific advertising. You can manage your cookie settings in your browser.

We also use Google Analytics to find out more about the behavior of our customers. This data is anonymised and only accessible to employees who we think reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products and services to our customers and to do their jobs effectively. This information is never shared or sold.

**EDITING YOUR ACCOUNT**

If you have an account with us, you can edit your name, billing/shipping addresses, telephone number, password and email address at any time. You can request to have your account with us deleted at any time by emailing [infodelete@peggsandson.com](mailto:infodelete@peggsandson.com).
